RECIPE REALM

Recipe Realm Privacy Policy
---------------------------

Here at Recipe Realm we take your privacy very seriously. The following document outlines how we process your information.  
Last updated: 03/05/24  
Effective date: 03/05/24  

### Definitions

"We", "us", "Recipe Realm", "the service" reffers to Recipe Realm, the website accessable via https://recipe-realm.com  
"You", "the visitor" reffers to you, the person accessing the service.  
"Service Providers", "providers" reffers to third parties that provides services to us such as hosting and CDNs.  

#### 1) Automated Collection of Information

We and our service providers may collect some information for you when you visit our website.  
Under the General Data Protection Regulation("GDPR"), and the California Consumer Privacy Act("CCPA") we may collect Personally Identifiable Information("PII")  

* Your IP address and estimated geographical location.

We also collect some non-PII under the GDPR/CCPA.  

* Date and time of your visit.
* Your user-agent which includes information such as operating system, browser and browser version.
* The web-page that linked you to us.

You can also create an account. If you choose to do this, you will need to provide the information provided in Clause 4.  

#### 2) Disclosure of Information

We and our service providers may use information obtained via the usage of the Service to  

* Analyze usage trends
* Improve the performance and functionality of our website
* Deliver personalized advertisements

#### 3) Disclosure of Information

The sale of personal information is defined very broadly. As a result we may have sold your personal data. You can opt out of the sale and/or sharing of your personal information by clicking the cookie icon in the bottom left corner and rejecting marketing cookies.  
We may share non-information with service providers that help us operate our website, such as hosting providers and analytics providers.  
These service providers are bound by confidentiality agreements and are not authorized to use the personal information for any purpose other than to provide services to us.  

#### 4) Log-in Services

We use Auth0's log-in services to allow users to create accounts. If you choose to create an account, Auth0 collects and shares with us the following, which may include PII.  

* Your e-mail address
* The username of your social account if using one to log in.
* The profile picture of your social account if using one to log in.
* A unique user id

#### 4) Web Beacons

We utilize some web beacons (also known as "clear pixels", "clear gifs") in order to aggregate statistical data about our sites users, such as  

* Your IP address and estimated geographical location
* Your user agent
* Referring web pages
* What pages you visit
* The loading time of the visit

This information is used to analyze website traffic, user behavior, and demographics.  
We use the following web beacons/trackers:

* Google Analytics
* Cloudflare Pixel/Beacon
* Microsoft Clarity
* Sentry
* Matomo (formally known as Pikwik)

We use this information to improve our website and provide a better user experience.  

#### 5) Google Adsence

We make use of Google Adsence on our website. Google AdSense uses cookies and other tracking technologies to display advertisements that may be of interest to you based on the websites that you visit.  

#### 6) Do Not Track

Some internet browsers allow you to set a Do Not Track("DNT") header/signal that is sent to websites.  
We do not respond to these signals, which means we will continue to serve targetted advertisements and use web beacons if these signals are set.  

#### 7) Childrens Privacy

We do not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13.  
If you become aware that a Child has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us.  
If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from Children, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.  

#### 8) Changes to this policy

We will routinley update this policy. As and when we do that, we will update the updated date at the top of this policy.  
Changes will come into effect immediatley after they are made.  
We do not reserve the right to notify you after a policy change, which means you should periodicly recheck this policy.  
By using this website after a policy change, you accept the policy changes.
